{
"question": "上",
"answer": "うえ"
},
{
"question": "悪い",
"answer": "わるい"
},
{
"question": "教える",
"answer": "おしえる"
},
{
"question": "降る",
"answer": "ふる"
},
{
"question": "死ぬ",
"answer": "しぬ"
},
{
"question": "帰る",
"answer": "かえる"
},
{
"question": "忘れる",
"answer": "わすれる"
},
{
"question": "多い",
"answer": "おおい"
},
{
"question": "出掛ける",
"answer": "でかける"
},
{
"question": "若い",
"answer": "わかい"
},
{
"question": "掛かる",
"answer": "かかる"
},
{
"question": "同じ",
"answer": "おなじ"
},
{
"question": "起きる",
"answer": "おきる"
},
{
"question": "座る",
"answer": "すわる"
},
{
"question": "店",
"answer": "みせ"
},
{
"question": "入れる",
"answer": "いれる"
},
{
"question": "何方-1",
"answer": "どなた"
},
{
"question": "一寸-1",
"answer": "ちょっと"
},
{
"question": "疲れる",
"answer": "つかれる"
},
{
"question": "開ける",
"answer": "あける"
},
